Who killed?
Who killed?  You tell me the truth, friend.   It seemed
too fast.
Dude, it's hurting.
[laughs]
Oh my, your body.  [laughter]
[music]
He was just shaking [laughter]
brother.
Shut up.
So hello guys welcome to my new vlog
video.
Good sir.
So guys, welcome to today's vlog.
Brother, we have just come to Lucknow and are roaming around
in Lucknow.  Now we are going to Alamat Dham.
Ok?  What do you say like Alamat Dham?   The
location in Lucknow is very good.  It
is a very nice place.  There is a temple there.  Ok
?  Let's go.  Since we have come to Lucknow,
we should also have darshan of God.
Ok.  So brother, I want to tell
you all to stay tuned to today's love blog.
Ok?  So today too we are going to have a lot of
fun.
We will meet the same sister-in-law who came here three years ago.  I know
brother.  Look brother Om,
what should I tell you, Bhabhi was very nice, that's why I am asking you to
wait for a while, come on brother, let's go for
a small darshan and then go straight to
Hanuman Dham and first let you guys have darshan
of the Lord, after that we will make
you guys enjoy, okay come on
[Music]
So finally guys we have reached, no one will say anything,
Halmat
Bham
[Music]
So guys, Bajrangbali is here.  Ok.
Ok.
Jai bajarangabalee.
Say [music] say it.
No one said anything, friend.  Nobody spoke.  No one has the courage to speak.
Tell me this is a lie.   Let's
go brother and it felt great.  I felt very
relaxed after visiting this place.  Let's
get out of here now.  So come on brother, I have seen
God.  Now let's go out and
entertain you all.  Ok
?  So
now the real fun begins.  So finally guys, after wandering around
we reached Insaan.   I ca
n't help it [laughs].
These people have come.  Look brother, he is injured.
Show me your eyes brother.  He got hurt.  We went there to jump.   Show me
how to do jumping once.
Nothing happened to other brothers like this.  He was in pain
yesterday.  No, my
love, I understood.
[laughter]
Where was it hurting?
Where was the pain?
Say that your back is paining
[Music]
No talk, when your back is paining you can enjoy it [Music]
[Laughter]
Come on brother, let's go today, we are going to
Janeshwar Park, okay,
one beautiful sister-in-law has come to Janeshwar Park, okay, come on brother, let's
see and let you guys enjoy
today's lovely blog, come on, finally guys,
we have reached with them.  He came today also.
[MUSIC] You
know, it's been coming for three days straight.
Brother, as far as I think, she has
not been coming with me for the last three-four days.   It is a
great insult at the same time.
As far as I think, I might fall in love
or she might fall in love with
me.
You don't have to.
Hey, just do it
[music].
Is the payment online?  Do it online.  Brother, I have asked you to wait for the
payment.  I am the one bearing the
expenses.  So
finally guys got the ticket.  Both of us
got tickets to Goa.   Let's go and
enjoy in Goa.
We will have a great honeymoon.
[MUSIC] It's just so
beautiful right now.
Damn,
oh damn [laughs]
it's so beautiful so far.   I have been
cheated brother.
So where did brother go?
Hey brother, where are you?  Yes
Bhabhi, brother, this is the Bhabhi who came to Lucknow for the
first time, so I did not meet you, where are
you from, I am
from Bihar, right,
from Samastipur,
yes
Bhabhi had said that I like your video very much,
yes guys, finally after three years we have met again
and this is for you,
oh man,
oh man, this is a different fraud going on, get
ready, I am ready [Music] get ready
brother, what do you mean, why have you brought
this, I have come to give it to her, with love, with
love, I will not give anything else.
I love you [laughs]
Hey
bastard, just say I love you.   Oh no no,
I will not take it like this.   No no,
I
love you brother-in-law, say it
[music]
wrong, right?
Hey brother-in-law, you can tell me, right?
Ok, good.  Take it brother-in-law.   By
saying I love you.   By
saying I love you [laughs].
Say.  Is she your sister?
Yes, she stays with me [sound of clearing throat].
I mean she is a friend, a sister, you can consider her as
everything.   She
lives with me.
So brother, we will also take his sister's
reaction.
Yes yes
video reaction.
[Music]
But we tell him I love you [Laughter]
straight away
Raja ji guys ever since
Bhabhi came my pants are getting stuck
from below I don't know what has happened
[Music]
what is this
yes it seems something is going to happen yes ever since she came my
pants were not slipping
Bhabhi like this Bhabhi like this now he has started keeping it like this
[Music]
so guys Bhabhi is asking about him.
She is not a dancer, sister-in-law.   Please
fix my YouTube channel.
Tell me who is this?
This is our stuff.  Ok.   You are a
big bastard, son.
Okay,
now we will take their reaction.  Reaction
reaction reaction [MUSIC].
A. In limits.   All of them.   I will
not be in any trouble at all.
I will also give.  One time reaction.  You bastard
[laughs]
now I will take a reaction once.
Well, there is
no fun in giving as there is in receiving [laughs]
Bhabhi, you tell me.
Brother, stop it, friend, stop it.
So guys, we met Bhabhi around
January 3rd, 2026, 2024, we met her on
January 8th.  Ok?  I had met him before.  So
sister-in-law was feeling very shy.  Ok.  So
sister-in-law always gets upset.  Sister-in-law had a habit of laughing.
So she became a little fatter than before.  Got dirty.
[laughs] Oh mom, it's not like that, guys,
I have thyroid, still I follow a strict
diet, I eat
something good, it does
n't increase fat in the body,
so I
would like to tell you that you might not be able to get Bhaiya's tonic,
so friends, please put it away,
understood
[music]
So tell me one thing Bhabhi, I have a question for you, okay,
do you want to go to the moon, no, no, I don't want to go,
you are fond of going, never, not at all, not at all, not
sure,
yes, you are fond of going to the moon?
No.
Hey, just tell me.  Yes, I like to go.
Why should I say it?
We are two friends.  I thought brother, let's make both of them
sit in the rocket.   It's a
rocket.  Look, there's a rocket back and forth.
Do you like playing with rockets?  [laughter]
This one's turkey.
Come on brother.   Don't
play at all.
what did you say?  what did you say?
We never played with fake toys.   Only when
we
play will you know
how to become a mother.   I will become
Lara
whenever I have to.   If I become one then there will be
no need for the previous one.
I know brother, I will have to work hard.   No
problem, I will do it.
Whoever wants to do it will do it.  Why would you
do that?
Brother, because I am your future husband, that is why I will do it.
[Music] I'll
make everyone my husband on the road.
Look, the one
above us
creates our pair by writing it.  Ok?  I have already
written our pair.  Do you know how?
God knows one thing,
he came to Lucknow for three-four days.  Ok?   I
mean, I have met him only for three days.  So
tell me friend, they are a couple, there must be
something special.   there must be
something.
I am meeting him every day.   I
get its
reaction every day in my brother's blog every three days.  So
[laughs]
stop like this
I am a very tough guy but friend
I melted here [music]
to me you are lovely
[music]
guys there is a cycle here they want to cycle the cycle they want to cycle it
so ride my cycle
put gears in it okay you know I will be
completely successful in just one gear it is I am
[laughs] happy with this shut up.
Guys she is speaking English.  I love you.
I hate you.
I kiss you.  I don't like you.
Your lips [laughs] are as red as a rose.
So guys, both of them are saying this to praise us.  Should I
praise you too?   No no,
I did not say that.
Brother, should I praise you?
No.   Okay,
fine.  I will praise you.  wait.   Yes, please do it.
Sing a song, sing a song for us too.
Before singing the song, other guys praise each other.
Oh my God, your body [laughs]
[music]
friend, what a compliment friend [laughs] friend, I praised you,
sorry Bhabhi, sorry, sorry, it's just a joke, should I
sing a song for you, the one you were
singing right now,
Ae Gori, hum Mithila mein Atoot to Ghuman shehar
Sajila mein Bhaji ke bahiya chhod tora humra se
nahi na mila, sing the song Je humra se pregnant Bhajo se, brother, I want to sing a song for both of them, we are number one, both of us are stupefied, come on, thank you, we have a charm, friend, if you got hurt, press it harder, press it harder, it hurts more than it should, friend, it's
paining friend
[laughs] on
love, guys,
Bhabhi has got another sister.
Sorry sorry sorry sorry, there was a
problem.   I don't have a
sister.
Hey, no, no,
I thought she was beautiful.  Thank you.
[laughter]
So guys, it was raining here.  Ok.
Rain water was coming.  Bhabhi is saying,
I told Bhabhi, Bhabhi, don't come.  Your
makeup will wash off.
So you are saying that I just apply lipstick.
Yes.  So brother, you know you have come to your brother-in-law.
So if possible, your lipstick will also be erased.
Okay,
yes, do you
understand?   Do you
know?  Thank you brother.  But friend, you
take your girlfriend out.
I didn't like it, friend.  [laughter] Come on, brother.
Yes I am Guddu Blog.
Yes brother.   That's why I am
stopping.
So brother, sister-in-law's lipstick will fade away in a short time.
Baji ho
keli
baap re
arre dada re [Music]
baap re baap re bhaiya sahab the way her waist swayed listen listen
listen [Laughter] just
look at yourselves one second her waist swayed looks
awesome come on come on come on come on
but sit comfortably it is okay
maybe the dholli will be seen then which
song is this?  Dhori wala hai,
we will become it.  You become my sister-in-law.  I am
not listening to you brother-in-law.  She is ignoring it.
Now she is slowly ignoring it.  No problem.  She
is my sister-in-law.  Oh Bhabhi [laughs] she is
my Bhabhi, isn't she brother?  Let me ignore it.
All the brothers who are Aai's daughters, ignore them and
spit on them.
So guys, just dance and say sorry sorry
once, slow down your dance steps, slowly.
Sorry [laughs] sorry since
then brother I mean it was shaking in the body
shut up
hey friend listen if you ask me what was
your t-shirt shaking look the t-shirt is
peeling off [music] how will he say show me show me the
video ok show me the
video show me
who is this dhala
so brother both of them are shooting ok
this girl is ignoring me.  Ok.
[MUSIC]
Never mind.  I have a sister-in-law.
[Music] I'll manage
with Bhabhi, brother.
No, sister-in-
law also has a friend, you can check with her also.   Look,
she was hugging just now.  Come on brother.  [laughs]
[ __ ], man.
Let me bring water.   There is
no water, friend.
I am bringing it.
Take it quickly, quickly.   Take me
sitting in it.  In the pump.
No, it is grass, it is grass
brother, it is a joke, come on
brother, come on, sorry, sorry, you want to
drink water, I will bring it for you, wait, if you want to drink water then come, I will
pee next to you
[laughs] no, it should not be so dirty, it should not be deleted, it should not happen, nothing, I am his friend brother, it is okay, I have become his friend in Lucknow, today slowly it is enough today only [laughs]
tomorrow, then tomorrow everything will be over,
brother, today today we are leaving brother, we are leaving forever
brother.
No brother, don't go forever.  Take them away.   We will
not take them with us.  I can't take you with me.   Okay,
I will go.
But I will take this also.
You seem like a nice guy, friend.
Oh, run away
[laughs] I liked
this too.  Shake hands.   I
will mix it up.   You are
betraying me.
A hello
you hello.   Do you
know what if I kill you?  You will become straight Gabin.  I will tell you.
I will say this again and again [laughter].  So never hit
me.  Ok.
Show me how you hit me the way I did.  Hit yeah one
second
[music]
[laughter]
explain to your friend, bro, she's killing me.
Okay [laughs]
So guys, I'm thirsty.  Ok.  I
want Bhabhi to give me
water to drink with your lips.  Yes.   No no, I didn't say this, I was going to say this
brother.
Pya Dil Mera [Music]
Bhabhi, I want to
drink this [laughs]
No
brother, you get a bottle there for ₹300, sorry it
slipped out of my mouth [laughs] I
mean, let me
tell you one thing for ₹20, let's
go and eat biryani, we will eat
biryani for ₹370,
okay, will you eat it or
not, I will eat it, I will pay for it.
You will drop me home.   It cost
₹70 but I will recover it.
Hey
brother, this happens, I am joking.  Ok.
This is my friend.  You are joking.  Sorry
friend.
How did you say it?  How?
It's okay friend.
Sister-in-law, where are you feeling pain?   I have a
headache.   Should I
massage your head?   Yes
definitely.  No brother,
this is
Amma,
you just choked me,
why did you choke me brother, she
said choke me,
then choke me, I will make a sound, hey
why did you do it brother
[screaming sound]
[laughter]
ch [
laughter]
I liked this fear.
[music]
[laughter]
Why do you abuse me, brother?  Sorry, my ass got torn.
[laughs]
It's already torn, brother.
Guys, there's a swing here.  Ok.  Sister-in-law, come and
sit.  So guys, Bhabhi is very overweight.  How much do
you weigh?
Why should I tell?   Come.
Come on, come on.   Come on.
This is what is fun.
Hey, I am [laughs] No, hey, I am, I will
pick you up.
I am yours very good you get up.   I will pick it up
slowly, you will enjoy it.
You get up, get up from above.   I will
enjoy it.
You get up and move away.
Now I will do it.  Get up, get up, sit down
[laughter].   Sit, sit.
I will not sit on the swing.
Hey, sit down, sit down.
Brother please.
No, you will get hurt.  I will get
hurt.
I am here.
My clothes will get dirty.
Sit comfortably and you will enjoy it.
No problem.  Is sister-in-law mine or yours?  Be
quiet.
Read.
No.  brother sit sit
sit [laughter] nothing will happen
look I am
not wearing it
you sit come on
I will not wear these
sit sit do
n't come and sit [laughter]
not with them she is the one who started misbehaving
so brother the
girl is starting to misbehave
and let's do this with love [laughter]
let's do it with love
let's do it with love we will call out
brother don't get too excited come do it do it
mine will burst [laughter]
everyone is bad man
god
so brother Sunny bhai got hurt he got dizzy
look brother Sunny bhai what happened who did he
fainted
[laughter] don't act stupid okay
who did it who did it
brother Sunny bhai got hurt friend who did it a
lot
brother
who did it brother
brother tell me tell me who did it I am
saying did he
break the game tell me who did it
[laughter] I did
not do it I
made a video
who did it tell me
break the bastard
brother look he hit him a lot okay look he
hit Sunny bhai a lot friend who hit him who hit
you tell me friend you tell me
[laughter]
so guys here  Aunty fell down, I do
n't know where she is crying, she was laughing,
you were laughing
[laughs] I was going to
swing me.
Bhabhi, it is not your turn.
If you do this to me, I am telling you, I will
beat you very badly. I will catch you all and
bite you.
Hey [screaming]
[music]
So, bro, we just came to the bathroom.  Ok
?  Grandma had fallen at that time.  Understood?  We went
first to pick up the confusion.  Is she laughing
or crying?  When I found out that she was
laughing, then the video started [laughter]
meaning one eye was closed like that.  Ok.   The
mouth was out.
Everyone thought she was crying.  What
happened to the eye?   She is
laughing and crying.  I can't figure it out.
[laughter]
Come on, Guys.
We just finished hugging and peeing.  There is urine in it.
Ok.  [laughs]
So guys, Bhabhi just called me crazy.
Corrected.  Do you know what?  I have gone crazy, crazy since then
I am in your love
[Music]
No no no no
Holi happened brother
Holi
so brother Bhabhi how did you like Holi
I don't like Holi I do
n't like Holi with this brother in law I do
n't like playing Holi with anyone I do
n't like Holi
hey I will apply colours to you you
colour me
shut up you dog I have
met Babuji here in the guys park.
Okay Babuji, please get our number impressed
Babuji, go
brother, she has almost been impressed in three days,
almost 70% impressed, the remaining 30% of which is left brother, you will go to
someone else
tomorrow, go, you will go tomorrow, right? Yes,
I am going right now,
you will go today, that 70% is over, that was
70%, don't know
how to express your love to her brother, songs [music], I know
how to sing, it was
from your side, right? So I am telling you from your side, from
my side
you go to this girl [laughs]
okay okay okay,
I am making a vlog.  Who cares for his own interests
?
I am hitting the blog.   With this
look
in your eyes,
I want to go to my home.
So finally guys, we have come back after shooting the video
and now it is about to be 10:00.
Ok?  And I am leaving for Delhi.
Ok?  Although we are in Sunny Bhai's
room, look here,
brother Sunny Bhai,
brother I have done as much as I could, we don't have our own house
and it is good to cook food.
Then someday we will have our own house, then Guddu Bhai will be
served well. Okay brother, no
problem, there is no lack in service, no
problem brother, brother, everyone lives together like this,
every time I have a different thing [laughs]
Okay, okay, there was no lack of anything brother,
okay
[laughs]
Okay brother, how did you like this blog, please tell me by commenting with love.
Okay, see you in the next vlog, then
love you, bye, take care.